Dominique Paige

Houston, Texas, United States



dominiquepaige91@gmail.com



832-863-4357



linkedin.com/in/dominique-paige-2b575998

Summary

Passionate instructor/developer with 8 years of experience contributing to open-source projects, maintaining strict coding standards, instructing students in virtual and in-person classroom setting.

Accustomed to working in fast-paced and deadline driven environments

Experience with game development engines such as: Roblox, Unity, Unreal, Godot, Construct 3, and GameMaker

Experience



Unity VR Developer

MetaverseOne

Jul 2022 - Present (1 month +)

Creating an open source multiplayer VR Unity project.

Saving and storing player information on server using JSON.

Customizing and creating VR emulator controls for VR and non-VR users.

Attend meetings to showcase development in projects.

🧀 Instructor - Unity

STEAM K-12

Jun 2022 - Present (2 months +)

Attend meetings with owner and instructor regarding class schedules and updates.

Host weekly classes with small group students via Outschool.

Prior experience with Zoom

Prior expereince with Unity and Roblox.

Develop new curriculum courses.

Curriculum Developer

Chasewood Learning

Dec 2021 - Present (8 months +)

Developed online video courses and curriculum lessons for instructors

Instructed students in small groups virtually via Zoom

Prior experience in Roblox and Python

Created a new Construct 3 curriculum for instructors.

Responsible for keeping up with tasks involving the development of curriculum.

Curriculum Developer and Instructor

Curriculum Developer and Instructor

Magikid Robotics Lab

Nov 2020 - Present (1 year 9 months +)

Created PowerPoint style presentations with written curriculum lessons.

Developed curriculum lessons using Scratch, Python, and Unity.

Attend weekly live training meetings for new curriculum lessons and updates.

Coached students during NASA Space Apps Challenge.

Instructed students to develop apps using Python and PyCharm.

Prepare coursework, present workshops and training.



🔽 Curriculum Developer

PionCreator

Jan 2022 - Jul 2022 (7 months)

Develop curriculum lessons and videos for instructors.

Host weekly free-trial class for students who want to sign up for lessons.

Repsonsible for updating and collaborating with management on the development process of curriculum.

Attend weekly meetings with management and design team.

Prior experience with Python, Scratch, Roblox and Unity,

Prior experience with Zoom.

Experienced with programming languages such as Lua,.

Experienced with teaching students within the age group of 7 - 14.

☐ Roblox Developer

Thinkingbox

Apr 2022 - May 2022 (2 months)

Attend virtual weekly meetings with development discussing accomplishments and current task.

Prior Roblox experience.

Responsible for updating and logging bug reports and completion for task.

Uploading updated scripts via Git

Develop a character costume creator for players to customize their characters.

Save and load player data and avatar creations between games using Lua.

m Unity VR Developer

Starcade Studios

Sep 2021 - Dec 2021 (4 months)

Attend weekly meetings with development discuss updates regarding the development of escape room and stacking VR Games.

Develop functional VR/XR controls for multiplayer games.

Add gameplay functionality to VR games such as score keeping, player tracking, and trigger events.

Prior experience with Unity3D.

Logging and providing feedback with gameplay and multiplayer functionality.

Prior experience with Photon Networking.



Construct 3 Developer

Paradigm Learning

Oct 2021 - Nov 2021 (2 months)

Create a click and drag board game using game assets provided by company.

Develop and design game play functionality using HTML event sheets in Construct 3.

Attend scheduled meetings with owner.

Roblox Developer

John Allsopp

May 2021 - Aug 2021 (4 months)

Develop an online conference integration space for Roblox users.

Create add on features to enhance gameplay.

Design UI interface and layout of player menus and chat rooms.

Create weekly meetings for updates on project development.

Prior experience to Roblox Studio development.

Curriculum Developer/Instructor(Roblox)

TechDevAcademy

Apr 2020 - Aug 2021 (1 year 5 months)

Instructed students in small groups and individually virtually via Zoom.

Attend weekly meetings with staff members regarding new lessons and curriculums.

Hosted online summer and fall coding camps.

Developed online videos insturctional courses for Roblox game development lessons via Youtube.

Fast paced, dealine driven environment.

Unreal Developer

MoonCat, LLC

Apr 2021 - Jul 2021 (4 months)

Create gameplay mechanics for RPG such as dialogue, weapon system, and AI follow.

Using Unreal multiplayer system to recognize player interactions with clients and server.

Create player controls using Unreal's blueprint system.

Unity 3d Developer

Leonor Urena

Nov 2020 - Jun 2021 (8 months)

Develop an online multiplayer learning platform for students and instructors to learn.

Develop and build activities that tie in with lessons and concept of the courses built.

Save and load user information using Playfab Integration.

Create a simulator of a work-place experience using Fungus Integration.

Attend weekly to discuss updates and development of project.

மு Unity Game Developer

Gamerjibe

Apr 2020 - Jul 2020 (4 months)

Help develop and maintain online social networking platform.

Prior experience in Unity3D.

Worked closely with engineering and networking to develop new add-ons for online experience and features.

Experience with Photon Networking.

Attend virtually meetings with development and networking team via Discord.

Jr Curriculum Developer and Instructor

Code Ninjas

Apr 2018 - Mar 2020 (2 years)

Multi-task and work in face paced environment.

Developed online curriculum, training handbooks and presentations.

Perform face to face presentations at learning centers.

Prior Unity3D game development experience.

Prior virtual instructing experience.

Collaborated with marketing, web development, and development team with problem solving and feedback with online curriculum.

Worked with students in small group and individually.



Curriculum Developer

PETAL et al., NFP

Jun 2014 - Mar 2016 (1 year 10 months)

Developed online video courses, lessons, and activities for enrolled students.

Taught students how to create 3D models in Blender and how to develop games in Unity3D.

Instructed students individually and in groups, utilizing various teaching methods.

Knowledge of online platforms for teaching including Google and Skype.

Prioritize task and perform multiple tasks simultaneously.



Graphic Designer

Gamer Fit Nation

Jun 2014 - Aug 2014 (3 months)

Worked with departments across the company, including marketing and project management, in developing new ideas, initiatives, products, and services

Assists in the design and development of layouts for marketing materials, using appealing graphics that are well-organized.

Responsible to incorporate current design trends into each unique layout to produce an up-to-date style for custom ads.

Ability to exercise good judgment when interpreting instructions and to identify the strengths and weaknesses of alternative solutions.

Utilize strong written skills and bring effective visual ideas from concept through to completion.

Education

Houston Community College

Associate of Science - AS, Animation, Interactive Technology, Video Graphics and Special Effects

2010 - 2016



Alief Taylor High School

High School Diploma, General Studies 2006 - 2010

Skills

C++ • Blueprint • Python • Robotics • Instructional Design • Python (Programming Language) • Gitlab • Virtual Reality (VR) • Multiplayer Design • Photon

Honors & Awards

Scholastic Texas Art Education – Visual Arts - Scholastic Texas Art Education
Mar 2010

Study Breaks Magazine Contest Winner - Study Breaks
Feb 2015